<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Suite</title>
    <link>https://www.suite.social</link>
    <description>All-in-one Social Management, Marketing, Monitoring, Messaging and Merchant Platform!</description>

    <item>
      <title>Amazon Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Amazon.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Amazon is an American multinational technology company focusing on e-commerce, cloud computing, online advertising, digital streaming, and artificial intelligence. It has been referred to as "one of the most influential economic and cultural forces in the world. Post, plan or promote your amazon products to social networks using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:60 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behance Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Behance.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Behance (stylized as Bēhance) is a social media platform owned by Adobe whose main focus is to showcase and discover creative work. Users can sign up to Behance and build profiles consisting of projects. Both registered and unregistered users can view any particular project, as well as comment on them. Members of Behance can follow other users' profiles. Post, plan or promote to Behance using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:60 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DeviantArt Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Deviantart.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; DeviantArt is an online art community that features artwork, videography and photography. DeviantArt started as a site connected with people who took computer applications and modified them to their own tastes, or who posted the applications from the original designs. As the site grew, members in general became known as artists and submissions as arts. Post, plan or promote to DeviantArt using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:60 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>Master Cook Aluminium Deep Biryani Pan with Wooden handle ...</title>
      <link>#</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="#"&gt;&lt;img src="https://encrypted-tbn0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRcVba1Pw3eGet5ZwpeYTjtBo4P2avtPluY00_XlJh6VqPi0OqFR-gBWIjH"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; 26cm High Quality Aluminium Deep Biryani Pan Wooden Handle; Curved side design pan. Flat base. Pan measurement Dia 26cm x height 10cm.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 16:35:12 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>#</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>Etsy Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Etsy.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Etsy is an e-commerce company focused on handmade or vintage items and craft supplies. These items fall under a wide range of categories, including jewelry, bags, clothing, home décor and furniture, toys, art, as well as craft supplies and tools. Items described as vintage must be at least 20 years old. The site follows in the tradition of open craft fairs, giving sellers personal storefronts where they list their goods for a fee. Post, plan or promote to Etsy using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:60 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>yes</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>Facebook Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Facebook.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Facebook allows you to connect with friends, family and other people you know. Share photos and videos, send messages and get updates. Post, plan or promote to Facebook pages, live and groups using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:59 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reddit Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Reddit.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Reddit is a social news aggregation, content rating, and discussion website. Registered users (commonly referred to as "Redditors") submit content to the site such as links, text posts, images, and videos, which are then voted up or down by other members. Posts are organized by subject into user-created boards called "communities" or "subreddits". Submissions with more upvotes appear towards the top of their subreddit and, if they receive enough upvotes, ultimately on the site's front page. Post, plan or promote to your subreddits using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Telegram Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Telegram.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Telegram Messenger is a globally accessible freemium, cross-platform, encrypted, cloud-based and centralized instant messaging (IM) service. The application also provides optional end-to-end encrypted chats, popularly known as secret chat and video calling, VoIP, file sharing and several other features. Users can send text and voice messages, make voice and video calls, and share an unlimited number of images, documents, user locations, animated stickers, contacts, and audio files. Users can also follow channels. Post, plan or promote to Telegram using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SMS Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/SMS.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Short Message/Messaging Service, commonly abbreviated as SMS, is a text messaging service component of most telephone, Internet and mobile device systems. It uses standardized communication protocols that let mobile devices exchange short text messages. An intermediary service can facilitate a text-to-voice conversion to be sent to landlines. SMS technology originated from radio telegraphy in radio memo pagers that used standardized phone protocols. The service allows users to send and receive messages of up to 160 characters (when entirely alpha-numeric) to and from mobiles. Post, plan or promote to social neyworks via SMS using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:55 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>TikTok Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/TikTok.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; TikTok, known in China as Douyin, is a short-form video hosting service. It hosts a variety of short-form user videos, from genres like pranks, stunts, tricks, jokes, dance, and entertainment with durations from 15 seconds to ten minutes. Post, plan or promote to your TikTok profile using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:54 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tumblr Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Tumblr.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Tumblr is a social networking service that allows users to post multimedia and other content to a short-form blog. Users can follow other users' blogs. Bloggers can also make their blogs private. Post, plan or promote to your Tumblr blog using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:53 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twitter Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Twitter.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Twitter is a microblogging and social networking service on which users post and interact with messages known as "tweets". From breaking news and entertainment to sports and politics, get the full story with all the live commentary. Post, plan or promote to your Twitter profile using Social Suite.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:52 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vimeo Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Vimeo.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Vimeo is a video hosting, sharing, and services platform provider. Vimeo focuses on the delivery of high-definition video across a range of devices. Vimeo's business model is through software as a service (SaaS). They derive revenue by providing subscription plans for businesses and video content producers. Vimeo provides its subscribers with tools for video creation, editing, and broadcasting, enterprise software solutions, as well as the means for video professionals to connect with clients and other professionals. Post, plan or promote to Vimeo using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>Vk Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Vk.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; VK is a Russian line media and social networking service. VK is available in multiple languages but it is predominantly used by Russian speakers. VK users can message each other publicly or privately, create groups, pages, and events; share and tag images, audio, and video; and play browser-based games. Post, plan or promote to your Vk profile using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:51 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve scheduled="yes">yes</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>WhatsApp Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Whatsapp.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; WhatsApp is an internationally available freeware, cross-platform, centralized instant messaging (IM) and voice-over-IP (VoIP). It allows users to send text and voice messages, make voice and video calls, and share images, documents, user locations, and other content. WhatsApp's client application runs on mobile devices, and can be accessed from computers. The service requires a cellular mobile telephone number to sign up. WhatsApp released a standalone business app called WhatsApp Business which can communicate with the standard WhatsApp client. Post, plan or promote via WhatsApp using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Wordpress.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; WordPress is a free and open-source content management system. Features include a plugin architecture and a template system, referred to within WordPress as Themes. WordPress was originally created as a blog-publishing system but has evolved to support other web content types including more traditional mailing lists and forums, media galleries, membership sites, learning management systems (LMS) and online stores. Post, plan or promote to your Wordpress blog using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:50 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Xing Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Xing.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; XING is a Hamburg-based career-oriented social networking site. The site is primarily focused on the German-speaking market, alongside XING Spain, and competes with the American platform LinkedIn. Post, plan or promote to Xing using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>	
    <item>
      <title>Youtube Screen</title>
      <link>https://socialscreens.biz</link>
      <description>&lt;a href="https://socialscreens.biz"&gt; &lt;img src="https://suite.social/images/networks/Youtube.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; YouTube is an online video sharing and social media platform. It is owned by Google, and is the second most visited website, after Google Search. YouTube has had an unprecedented social impact, influencing popular culture, internet trends, and creating multimillionaire celebrities. Post, plan or promote to your Wordpress blog using Social Suite. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:49 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>https://socialscreens.biz</guid>
      <approve>no</approve>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
